Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is fish food. Let me show you how
to make it. We're starting off with a
chocolate protein shake. You can also
substitute this for [music] fat-free
milk plus a scoop of chocolate protein
powder. And then all the dry ingredients
listed in the caption. We're going to
blend that up with an immersion blender
and throw in the freezer for at least 16
hours. Once it's completely frozen
through, you can take it out and run it
under hot water for about 30 to 60
seconds. Then throw it in your creamy on
the light ice cream setting. And guys, I
used to buy Ben & Jerry's all the time
and fish food was by far my favorite
flavor. But then I realized it had
almost 1,200 calories and that was just
not going to work with my fitness goals.
So instead of eating Ben & Jerry's every
night, I just make it at home in a way
that will help me reach my goals and not
deter me from reaching my goals. To
maximize the protein in this, I'm using
a protein chocolate bar. If you can't
find these or they're not available in
your area, I would just go with the
chocolate chip hack that I've made a ton
of videos about. Just search up FPF
chocolate chip hack and it should pop
up. Then we're using some of these
Jetpuff mini marshmallows. These are
really good in ice cream. They add a
nice crunch and obviously that
marshmallow flavor. So, I mixed in 3/4
of that mixture and then put the last
quarter on top. And of course, fish
fruit isn't complete without some
caramel syrup. So, we're drizzling a
little bit on top. Comment which flavor
I should recreate